Guide to the Robert Fridenberg Collection of Portrait and Topographical Prints
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Portraits, Series I
  - F
    - Fielding, Henry, 1707-1754 (Box 76, Folder 1278)
    - Fiennes, Nathaniel, 1607 or 8-1669 (Box 76, Folder 1279)
    - Fieschi (Box 76, Folder 1280)
    - Fife (Box 76, Folder 1281)
    - Filangieri, Gaetano, 1752-1788 (Box 76, Folder 1282)
    - Finch of Fordwich, John Finch, Baron, 1584-1660 (Box 76, Folder 1283)
    - Fisher, Charles, 1816-1891
    - Fisher, Clara, 1811-1898
    - Fisher, Jane Lane, Lady, ca. 1626-1689 (Box 76, Folder 1284)
    - Fisher, John, saint, 1469-1535
    - Fitz-Alwyn, Henry, 1189-1211 (Box 76, Folder 1285)
    - Fitzgerald
    - Fitzgerald, Edward, 1763-1798 (Box 76, Folder 1286)
    - Fitzherbert
    - Fitzwilliam (Box 76, Folder 1287)
    - Flamsteed, John, 1646-1719 (Box 76, Folder 1288)
    - Flavel (Box 76, Folder 1289)
    - Flechier, Esprit, 1632-1710 (Box 76, Folder 1290)
    - Fleetwood, Charles, d. 1612 (Box 76, Folder 1291)
    - Fleming (Box 76, Folder 1292)
    - Fletcher (Box 76, Folder 1293)
    - Fletcher, Alexander, 1787-1860 (Box 76, Folder 1294)
    - Fletcher, Andrew, 1655-1716 (Box 76, Folder 1295)
    - Fletcher, John, 1579-1625 (Box 76, Folder 1296)
    - Fleury (Box 76, Folder 1297)
    - Fleury, Andre Hercule de, 1653-1743 (Box 76, Folder 1298)
    - Fleury, Claude 1640-1723 (Box 76, Folder 1299)
    - Flood, Henry, 1732-1791
    - Florence, William Jermyn, 1831-1891 (Box 76, Folder 1300)
    - Florent (Box 76, Folder 1301)
    - Florian, Jean-Piere, 1755-1794 (Box 76, Folder 1302)
    - Floris (Box 76, Folder 1303)
    - Foix, Pierre de, 1386-1464 (Box 76, Folder 1304)
    - Folkes, Martin, 1690-1754 (Box 76, Folder 1305)
    - Fontaine (Box 76, Folder 1306)
    - Fontanges, Marie Angelique de Scoraille de Rousille, duchesse de, 1661-1681 (Box 76, Folder 1307)
    - Fontenelle, M. de, 1657-1757 (Box 76, Folder 1308)
    - Foote, Maria, 1797-1867 (Box 76, Folder 1309)
    - Foote, Samuel, 1720-1777 (Box 76, Folder 1310)
    - Forbes (Box 76, Folder 1311)
    - Forbes, William, 1585-1634 (Box 76, Folder 1312)
    - Forbin (Box 76, Folder 1313)
    - Force, Duc de La (Box 76, Folder 1314)
    - Forman, Simon 1552-1611 (Box 76, Folder 1315)
    - Forrest, Edwin 1806-1872 (Box 76, Folder 1316)
    - Forster (Box 76, Folder 1317)
    - Fortescue (Box 76, Folder 1318)
    - Forth and Brentford, Patrick Ruthven, Earl of, 1573?-1651 (Box 76, Folder 1319)
    - Forteguerri, Niccolò, 1674-1735 (Box 76, Folder 1320)
    - Foscari (Box 77, Folder 1321)
    - Foscolo (Box 77, Folder 1322)
    - Foster (Box 77, Folder 1323)
    - Fouché (Box 77, Folder 1324)
    - Fourier (Box 77, Folder 1325)
    - Fouqé (Box 77, Folder 1326)
    - Fouquier-Tinville, Antoine Quentin, 1746-1795 (Box 77, Folder 1327)
    - Fox (Box 77, Folder 1328)
    - Fox, Charles James, 1749-1806 (Box 77, Folder 1329)
    - Foy (Box 77, Folder 1330)
    - France, Anatole, 1844-1924
    - Francesco Sforza, Duke of Milan, 1401-1466 (Box 77, Folder 1331)
    - Francis (Box 77, Folder 1332)
    - François II, Duke of Brittany, 1435-1488 (Box 77, Folder 1333)
    - François III, Duke of Brittany, 1518-1536 (Box 77, Folder 1334)
    - François de Neufchâteau, Nicolas Louis, comte, 1750-1828 (Box 77, Folder 1335)
    - Franklin (Box 77, Folder 1336)
    - Franklin, Benjamin, 1706-1790, 15 (Box 78, Folder 1337-1351)
    - Fraser (Box 79, Folder 1352)
    - Frazer (Box 79, Folder 1353)
    - Frederick Louis, Prince of Wales, 1707-1751
    - Frémont, John Charles, 1813-1890
    - French
    - Frere (Box 79, Folder 1354)
    - Fressinet (Box 79, Folder 1355)
    - Fréron, Elie-Catherine, 1718-1776 (Box 79, Folder 1356)
    - Fréteau de Saint-Just, Emmanuel-Marie-Michel-Philippe, 1745-1794 (Box 79, Folder 1357)
    - Freytag, Gustav, 1816-1895
    - Friedrich Ulrich, Duke of Brunswick-Wolfenbüttel, 1591-1634 (Box 79, Folder 1358)
    - Friedrich Wilhelm, Herzog von Braunschweig-Lüneburg-Oels, 1771-1815 (Box 79, Folder 1359)
    - Frobisher (Box 79, Folder 1360)
    - Froissart, Jean, 1338?-1410? (Box 79, Folder 1361)
    - Froude, James A., 1818-1894
    - Fry
    - Fry, Elizabeth Gurney, 1780-1845 (Box 79, Folder 1362)
    - Fualdès, Antoine-Bernardin, 1761-1817 (Box 79, Folder 1363)
    - Fuentes (Box 79, Folder 1364)
    - Fugger (Box 79, Folder 1365)
    - Fuller (Box 79, Folder 1366)
    - Fulton, Robert, 1765-1815 (Box 79, Folder 1367)
    - Oversize
      - Fa - Fz general, 7 (Box 80 (Oversize), Folder 1368-1374)
      - Fabert - Fitzwilliam, 37 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 1375-1411)
      - Flechier - Foy, 33 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 1412-1444)
      - France - Fuentes, 21 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 1445-1465)
  - G
    - Ga - Gl general, 6 (Box 84, Folder 1466-1471)
    - Go - Gz general, 6 (Box 85, Folder 1472-1477)
    - Gage (Box 86, Folder 1478)
    - Gage, Thomas, 1721-1787 (Box 86, Folder 1479)
    - Gale
    - Galen (Box 86, Folder 1480)
    - Galilei, Galileo, 1564-1642 (Box 86, Folder 1481)
    - Gales, Theodore
    - Gallatin, Albert, 1761-1849 (Box 86, Folder 1482)
    - Galsworthy, John, 1867-1933 (Box 86, Folder 1483)
    - Galt, John, 1779-1839 (Box 86, Folder 1484)
    - Gama, Vasco da, 1469-1524 (Box 86, Folder 1485)
    - Garder, Alan Garder, Baron, 1742-1809 (Box 86, Folder 1486)
    - Gardiner (Box 86, Folder 1487)
    - Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881 (Box 86, Folder 1488)
    - Garibaldi, Giuseppe, 1807-1882 (Box 86, Folder 1489)
    - Garnier (Box 86, Folder 1490)
    - Garrick, David, 1717-1779
    - Garth, Samuel, Sir, 1661-1719
    - Gascoigne (Box 86, Folder 1491)
    - Gassion, Jean, Comte de, 1609-1647 (Box 86, Folder 1492)
    - Gates, Horatio, 1728-1806 (Box 86, Folder 1493)
    - Gautier, Théophile, 1836-1904 (Box 86, Folder 1494)
    - Gay, John, 1685-1732
    - Gazēs, Theodōros, ca. 1400-ca. 1475 (Box 86, Folder 1495)
    - Gellert, Christian Fürchtegott, 1715-1769 (Box 86, Folder 1496)
    - Genlis, Stéphanie Félicité, comtesse de, 1746-1830 (Box 86, Folder 1497)
    - George, Prince, Duke of Cambridge, 1819-1904 (Box 86, Folder 1498)
    - Gerard (Box 86, Folder 1499)
    - Gerard, Etienne Maurice, 1773-1852 (Box 86, Folder 1500)
    - Gessner, Salomon, 1730-1788 (Box 86, Folder 1501)
    - Gevaerts, Jean-Gaspard, 1593-1666 (Box 86, Folder 1502)
    - Gibbon, Edward, 1737-1794 (Box 86, Folder 1503)
    - Gibson (Box 86, Folder 1504)
    - Gifford, William, 1756-1826 (Box 86, Folder 1505)
    - Gilbert (Box 87, Folder 1506)
    - Gilman, Nicholas, 1755-1814 (Box 87, Folder 1507)
    - Gilpin (Box 87, Folder 1508)
    - Girard, Stephen, 1750-1831 (Box 87, Folder 1509)
    - Girardin (Box 87, Folder 1510)
    - Gladstone, W. E. (William Ewart), 1809-1898 (Box 87, Folder 1511)
    - Gleig, George Robert, 1796-1888 (Box 87, Folder 1512)
    - Glencairn
    - Gloucester (Box 87, Folder 1513)
    - Glover, Phillis (Box 87, Folder 1514)
    - Glover, Richard, 1712-1785 (Box 87, Folder 1515)
    - Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787 (Box 87, Folder 1516)
    - Gneisenau, August Wilhelm Anton, Graf Neidhardt von, 1760-1831 (Box 87, Folder 1517)
    - Godefroy (Box 87, Folder 1518)
    - Godolphin, Earl of (Box 87, Folder 1519)
    - Godoy, Manuel de, principe de la Paz, 1761-1851 (Box 87, Folder 1520)
    - Godsalve, John (Box 87, Folder 1521)
    - Godwin, William, 1756-1836 (Box 87, Folder 1522)
    - Goes, van der (Box 87, Folder 1523)
    - Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von, 1749-1832 (Box 87, Folder 1524)
    - Goldoni, Carlo, 1707-1793 (Box 87, Folder 1525)
    - Goldsmith, Oliver, 1730-1774 (Box 87, Folder 1526)
    - Goncourt, Edmond de, 1822-1896 (Box 87, Folder 1527)
    - Gonzaga (Box 87, Folder 1528)
    - Goodman, Gabriel, 1528-1601
    - Goodwin, John, 1594-1665 (Box 87, Folder 1529)
    - Gorchakov (Box 87, Folder 1530)
    - Gordon (Box 88, Folder 1531)
    - Gordon, Robert, 1580-1661 (Box 88, Folder 1532)
    - Gore (Box 88, Folder 1533)
    - Gorham, Nathaniel, 1738-1796
    - Goring, George Goring, Baron, 1608-1657 (Box 88, Folder 1534)
    - Goschen, George Joachim Goschen, Viscount, 1831-1907 (Box 88, Folder 1535)
    - Gosse, Edmund, 1849-1928 (Box 88, Folder 1536)
    - Gough (Box 88, Folder 1537)
    - Gouvion Saint-Cyr, Laurent, marquis de, 1764-1830 (Box 88, Folder 1538)
    - Gower, John, 1325-1408 (Box 88, Folder 1539)
    - Gozzi (Box 88, Folder 1540)
    - Graff
    - Grafigny, Mme de (Françoise d'Issembourg d'Happoncourt), 1695-1758 (Box 88, Folder 1541)
    - Grafton (Box 88, Folder 1542)
    - Graham (Box 88, Folder 1543)
    - Graham, John, Viscount Dundee, 1648-1689 (Box 88, Folder 1544)
    - Gramont (Box 88, Folder 1545)
    - Granby (Box 88, Folder 1546)
    - Grandison, William Villiers, Viscount, 1614-1643 (Box 88, Folder 1547)
    - Granger, James, 1723-1776 (Box 88, Folder 1548)
    - Grant, Charles, 1778-1866 (Box 88, Folder 1549)
    - Grant, James, 1720 - 1806
    - Grant, Ulysses S. (Ulysses Simpson), 1822-1885 (Box 88, Folder 1550)
    - Granville (Box 88, Folder 1551)
    - Grasse, François Joseph Paul de Grasse, comte de, 1722-1788, and family (Box 88, Folder 1552)
    - Grattan, Henry, 1746 - 1820 (Box 88, Folder 1553)
    - Gray (Box 88, Folder 1554)
    - Gray, Thomas, 1716-1771 (Box 88, Folder 1555)
    - Grecourt, 1683-1743 (Box 88, Folder 1556)
    - Greeley, Horace, 1811-1872 (Box 88, Folder 1557)
    - Green (Box 88, Folder 1558)
    - Greene, Christopher (Box 89, Folder 1559)
    - Greene, Nathanael, 1742-1786 (Box 89, Folder 1560)
    - Gregoire, Henri, 1750-1831 (Box 89, Folder 1561)
    - Gregory
    - Gregory, Olinthus, 1774-1841 (Box 89, Folder 1562)
    - Grenville (Box 89, Folder 1563)
    - Gresham, Thomas, 1519?-1579 (Box 89, Folder 1564)
    - Gresset, 1709-1777 (Box 89, Folder 1565)
    - Gretry (Box 89, Folder 1566)
    - Grevy, Jules, 1807-1891 (Box 89, Folder 1567)
    - Grey (Box 89, Folder 1568)
    - Grier, Robert Cooper, 1794-1870 (Box 89, Folder 1569)
    - Griffin (Box 89, Folder 1570)
    - Grignan (Box 89, Folder 1571)
    - Grignan, Françoise Marguerite de Sévigné, comtesse de, 1646-1705 (Box 89, Folder 1572)
    - Grimaldi (Box 89, Folder 1573)
    - Grimm (Box 89, Folder 1574)
    - Grimston, Harbottle, 1603-1685 (Box 89, Folder 1575)
    - Gronovius, Jacob, 1645-1716 (Box 89, Folder 1576)
    - Grose, Francis, 1731?-1791 (Box 89, Folder 1577)
    - Grote, George, 1794-1871 (Box 89, Folder 1578)
    - Grotius, Hugo, 1583-1645 (Box 89, Folder 1579)
    - Guadet (Box 89, Folder 1580)
    - Gualtieri di Brienne, duca di Atene, d. 1356 (Box 89, Folder 1581)
    - Guebriant (Box 89, Folder 1582)
    - Guiccioli, Teresa, contessa di, 1800-1873 (Box 89, Folder 1583)
    - Guichen (Box 89, Folder 1584)
    - Guildford (Box 89, Folder 1585)
    - Guilhermy, Jean François César, baron de, 1761-1829 (Box 90, Folder 1586)
    - Guise (Box 90, Folder 1587)
    - Guizot, François, 1787-1874 (Box 90, Folder 1588)
    - Guizot, Madame (Elizabeth Charlotte Pauline), 1773-1827
    - Gurney (Box 90, Folder 1589)
    - Guthrie (Box 90, Folder 1590)
    - Gutenberg, Johannes, 1397-1469 (Box 90, Folder 1591)
    - Gwyn, Nell, 1650-1687 (Box 90, Folder 1592)
    - Oversize
      - Ga - Go general, 8 (Box 91 (Oversize), Folder 1593-1600)
      - Gr - Gz general, 4 (Box 92 (Oversize), Folder 1601-1604)
      - Gage - Gevaerts, 28 (Box 93 (Oversize), Folder 1605-1632)
      - Gibbon - Gonzaga, 23 (Box 94 (Oversize), Folder 1633-1655)
      - Goodman - Gray, 28 (Box 95 (Oversize), Folder 1656-1683)
      - Greeley - Gwyn, 28 (Box 96 (Oversize), Folder 1684-1711)
  - H
    - Ha - Herz general, 7 (Box 97, Folder 1712-1718)
    - Hes - Hy general, 7 (Box 98, Folder 1719-1725)
    - Habersham (Box 99, Folder 1726)
    - Haddington, Earl of
    - Hale, John P. (John Parker), 1806-1873 (Box 99, Folder 1727)
    - Hale, Matthew, Sir, 1609-1676 (Box 99, Folder 1728)
    - Hale, Nathan, 1755-1776
    - Halifax (Box 99, Folder 1729)
    - Hall (Box 99, Folder 1730)
    - Hall, John, 1627-1656 (Box 99, Folder 1731)
    - Hall, Joseph, 1574-1656 (Box 99, Folder 1732)
    - Hallam, Henry, 1777-1859 (Box 99, Folder 1733)
    - Hamilton (Box 99, Folder 1734)
    - Hamilton, Alexander, 1757-1804 (Box 99, Folder 1735)
    - Hamilton, Anthony, Count, ca. 1646-1720 (Box 99, Folder 1736)
    - Hamilton, Elizabeth Schuyler, 1757-1854 (Box 99, Folder 1737)
    - Hamilton, James, 1710-1783 (Box 99, Folder 1738)
    - Hamilton, James Hamilton, Duke of, 1606-1649 (Box 99, Folder 1739)
    - Hamilton, James Hamilton, Marquis of, 1589-1625 (Box 99, Folder 1740)
    - Hamilton, William Hamilton, Duke of, 1616-1651 (Box 99, Folder 1741)
    - Hamlin, Hannibal, 1809-1891
    - Hampden, John, 1594-1643 (Box 99, Folder 1742)
    - Hampton, Wade, 1818-1902 (Box 99, Folder 1743)
    - Hancock, John, 1737-1793 (Box 99, Folder 1744)
    - Hancock, Winfield Scott, 1824-1886 (Box 99, Folder 1745)
    - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759 (Box 99, Folder 1746)
    - Hanmer, Thomas, Sir, 1677-1746
    - Harcourt (Box 100, Folder 1747)
    - Harcourt, Henri de Lorraine, comte de, 1601-1666 (Box 100, Folder 1748)
    - Hardee, William Joseph, 1815-1873
    - Hardwicke (Box 100, Folder 1749)
    - Hardy (Box 100, Folder 1750)
    - Hare
    - Harlay (Box 100, Folder 1751)
    - Harley (Box 100, Folder 1752)
    - Harper (Box 100, Folder 1753)
    - Harrington (Box 100, Folder 1754)
    - Harrington, James, 1611-1677 (Box 100, Folder 1755)
    - Harris (Box 100, Folder 1756)
    - Harrison (Box 100, Folder 1757)
    - Harrowby (Box 100, Folder 1758)
    - Hartley (Box 100, Folder 1759)
    - Hastings (Box 100, Folder 1760)
    - Hastings, Francis Rawdon-Hastings, Marquess of, 1754-1826 (Box 100, Folder 1761)
    - Hastings, Warren, 1732-1818 (Box 100, Folder 1762)
    - Hatton, Christopher, Sir, 1540-1591 (Box 100, Folder 1763)
    - Hawke (Box 100, Folder 1764)
    - Hawkins (Box 100, Folder 1765)
    - Hawkwood, John, Sir, d. 1394 (Box 101, Folder 1766)
    - Hay (Box 101, Folder 1767)
    - Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809 (Box 101, Folder 1768)
    - Hayes (Box 101, Folder 1769)
    - Hazard
    - Hazlitt, William, 1778-1830 (Box 101, Folder 1770)
    - Heath (Box 101, Folder 1771)
    - Heber, Reginald, 1783-1826 (Box 101, Folder 1772)
    - Heemskerk (Box 101, Folder 1773)
    - Hein / Heyn (Box 101, Folder 1774)
    - Heine, Heinrich, 1797-1856 (Box 101, Folder 1775)
    - Héloïse, 1101-1164 (Box 101, Folder 1776)
    - Helvétius, 1715-1771 (Box 101, Folder 1777)
    - Hénault, Charles-Jean-François, 1685-1770 (Box 101, Folder 1778)
    - Henley (Box 101, Folder 1779)
    - Henriette, d'Angleterre, duchesse d'Orléans, 1644-1670 (Box 101, Folder 1780)
    - Henry (Box 101, Folder 1781)
    - Henry, Patrick, 1736-1799 (Box 101, Folder 1782)
    - Henry, Prince, Duke of Gloucester, 1640 - 1660 (Box 101, Folder 1783)
    - Herbert (Box 101, Folder 1784)
    - Herbert of Cherbury, Edward Herbert, Baron, 1583-1648. (Box 101, Folder 1785)
    - Herbert, George, 1593-1633 (Box 101, Folder 1786)
    - Herder, Johann Gottfried, 1744-1803 (Box 101, Folder 1787)
    - Heriot, George, 1563-1624 (Box 101, Folder 1788)
    - Herschel (Box 101, Folder 1789)
    - Hervey (Box 101, Folder 1790)
    - Hesse (Box 102, Folder 1791)
    - Hewit, John, 1614-1658 (Box 102, Folder 1792)
    - Hill (Box 102, Folder 1793)
    - Hill, Aaron, 1685-1750 (Box 102, Folder 1794)
    - Hill, Rowland, 1744-1833 (Box 102, Folder 1795)
    - Hill, Rowland Hill, Viscount, 1772-1842 (Box 102, Folder 1796)
    - Hill, Rowland, Sir, 1795-1879 (Box 102, Folder 1797)
    - Hill, Thomas, 1760-1840 (Box 102, Folder 1798)
    - Hiller (Box 102, Folder 1799)
    - Hobart (Box 102, Folder 1800)
    - Hobbes, Thomas, 1588-1679 (Box 102, Folder 1801)
    - Hobhouse (Box 102, Folder 1802)
    - Hobry, Marie, d. 1688 (Box 102, Folder 1803)
    - Hobson, Thomas, ca. 1544-1630 (Box 102, Folder 1804)
    - Hoche, Lazare, 1768-1797 (Box 102, Folder 1805)
    - Hodgkinson (Box 102, Folder 1806)
    - Hofer (Box 102, Folder 1807)
    - Hoffman (Box 102, Folder 1808)
    - Hogarth, William, 1697-1764 (Box 102, Folder 1809)
    - Hogg (Box 102, Folder 1810)
    - Hohenlohe (Box 102, Folder 1811)
    - Holcroft, Thomas, 1745-1809 (Box 102, Folder 1812)
    - Holland (Box 102, Folder 1813)
    - Holles, John, Earl of Clare, ca. 1565-1637 (Box 103, Folder 1814)
    - Holmes (Box 103, Folder 1815)
    - Holt, John, Sir, 1642-1710
    - Hood (Box 103, Folder 1816)
    - Hood, Samuel Hood, Viscount, 1724-1816 (Box 103, Folder 1817)
    - Hood, Thomas, 1799-1845 (Box 103, Folder 1818)
    - Hooft (Box 103, Folder 1819)
    - Hook, Theodore Edward, 1788-1841 (Box 103, Folder 1820)
    - Hooker (Box 103, Folder 1821)
    - Hoole, John, 1727-1803 (Box 103, Folder 1822)
    - Hoorne, Filips van Montmorency, Graaf van, 1524?-1568 (Box 103, Folder 1823)
    - Hopkins (Box 103, Folder 1824)
    - Hopkinson (Box 103, Folder 1825)
    - Hopton, Ralph Hopton, Baron, 1598-1652 (Box 103, Folder 1826)
    - Hoskins, John, 1634-1705
    - Hospital, Michel De, L', 1507-1573 (Box 103, Folder 1827)
    - Hotham, John, Sir, d. 1645 (Box 103, Folder 1828)
    - Houchard, Jean-Nicolas, 1738-1793 (Box 103, Folder 1829)
    - Houssaye, Arsène, 1815-1896 (Box 103, Folder 1830)
    - Howard (Box 103, Folder 1831)
    - Howe (Box 103, Folder 1832)
    - Howe, Richard Howe, Earl, 1726-1799 (Box 103, Folder 1833)
    - Howe, William Howe, Viscount, 1729-1814 (Box 103, Folder 1834)
    - Howell (Box 103, Folder 1835)
    - Howitt, Mary Botham, 1799-1888 (Box 103, Folder 1836)
    - Hoym (Box 103, Folder 1837)
    - Hudson (Box 103, Folder 1838)
    - Hughes (Box 103, Folder 1839)
    - Hugo, Victor, 1802-1885 (Box 104, Folder 1840)
    - Humboldt, Alexander von, 1769-1859 (Box 104, Folder 1841)
    - Hume, David, 1711-1776 (Box 104, Folder 1842)
    - Hume, Joseph, 1777-1855 (Box 104, Folder 1843)
    - Humphreys (Box 104, Folder 1844)
    - Hunsdon, Henry Carey, Baron, 1526-1596 (Box 104, Folder 1845)
    - Hunt (Box 104, Folder 1846)
    - Hunt, Leigh, 1784-1859 (Box 104, Folder 1847)
    - Hunter (Box 104, Folder 1848)
    - Huntington (Box 104, Folder 1849)
    - Huntington, Samuel, 1731-1796 (Box 104, Folder 1850)
    - Huntly, George Gordon, Marquess of, d. 1649 (Box 104, Folder 1851)
    - Hutchinson (Box 104, Folder 1852)
    - Hutton (Box 104, Folder 1853)
    - Oversize
      - Ha - He general, 9 (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 1854-1862)
      - Hi - Hz general, 6 (Box 106 (Oversize), Folder 1863-1868)
      - Haddington - Harrowby, 26 (Box 107 (Oversize), Folder 1869-1894)
      - Hastings - Hood, 34 (Box 108 (Oversize), Folder 1895-1928)
      - Hooft - Hutton, 35 (Box 109 (Oversize), Folder 1929-1963)
  - I
    - Ia - Iz general, 2 (Box 110, Folder 1964-1965)
    - Ibsen, Henrik, 1828-1906
    - Imperiali (Box 110, Folder 1966)
    - Ingersoll (Box 110, Folder 1967)
    - Inglis (Box 110, Folder 1968)
    - Iredell
    - Ireland
    - Ireton, Henry, 1611-1651 (Box 110, Folder 1969)
    - Irving (Box 110, Folder 1970)
    - Irving, Henry, Sir, 1838-1905
    - Irving, Washington, 1783-1859 (Box 110, Folder 1971)
    - Oversize
      - Ia - Iz general, 2 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 1972-1973)
      - Ibsen - Irving, 8 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 1974-1981)
  - J
    - Ja-Jz general, 5 (Box 112, Folder 1982-1986)
    - J. D. (John Dormer), 1636-1700
    - Jackson (Box 113, Folder 1987)
    - Jackson, Andrew, 1767-1845 - 2 folders, 2 (Box 113, Folder 1988-1989)
    - James (Box 113, Folder 1990)
    - James, G. P. R. (George Payne Rainsford), 1801?-1860 (Box 113, Folder 1991)
    - James, Rajah of Sarawak, 1803-1868 (Box 113, Folder 1992)
    - Jameson (Box 113, Folder 1993)
    - Janin, Jules Gabriel, 1804-1874 (Box 113, Folder 1994)
    - Jay (Box 113, Folder 1995)
    - Jay, John, 1745-1829, and Sarah Livingston Jay (Box 113, Folder 1996)
    - Jean, Duke of Brittany (all) (Box 113, Folder 1997)
    - Jean Paul, 1763-1825 (Box 113, Folder 1998)
    - Jeanne d'Albret, Queen of Navarre, 1528-1572 (Box 113, Folder 1999)
    - Jeannin, Pierre, 1540-1622 (Box 113, Folder 2000)
    - Jefferson, Joseph, 1829-1905 (Box 113, Folder 2001)
    - Jefferson, Thomas, 1732-1807 (Box 113, Folder 2002)
    - Jefferson, Thomas, 1743-1826, 2 (Box 113, Folder 2003-2004)
    - Jeffrey, Francis Jeffrey, Lord, 1773-1850 (Box 113, Folder 2005)
    - Jenkins (Box 113, Folder 2006)
    - Jerdan (Box 113, Folder 2007)
    - Jeroným, Pražský, ca. 1380-1416 (Box 114, Folder 2008)
    - Jerrold, Douglas William, 1803-1857
    - Joan, of Arc, Saint, 1412-1431 (Box 114, Folder 2009)
    - John, Archduke of Austria, 1782-1859 (Box 114, Folder 2010)
    - John, Duke of Burgundy, 1371-1419 (Box 114, Folder 2011)
    - John, of Austria, 1547-1578 (Box 114, Folder 2012)
    - John, of Austria, 1629-1679 (Box 114, Folder 2013)
    - John, of Gaunt, Duke of Lancaster, 1340-1399 (Box 114, Folder 2014)
    - Johnson (Box 114, Folder 2015)
    - Johnston (Box 114, Folder 2016)
    - Johnston, H. (Henry Erskine), 1777-1845, and Nannette, b. 1782 (Box 114, Folder 2017)
    - Johnstone (Box 114, Folder 2018)
    - Joinville (Box 114, Folder 2019)
    - Jones (Box 114, Folder 2020)
    - Jones, John Paul, 1747-1792 (Box 114, Folder 2021)
    - Jonson, Ben, 1573?-1637 (Box 114, Folder 2022)
    - Jordan, Dorothy, 1761-1816 (Box 114, Folder 2023)
    - Joseph, père, 1577-1638 (Box 114, Folder 2024)
    - Josephus, Flavius (Box 114, Folder 2025)
    - Joubert, Barthélemy Catherine, 1769-1799 (Box 114, Folder 2026)
    - Jourdan (Box 114, Folder 2027)
    - Joyeuse (Box 114, Folder 2028)
    - Junot, Jean Andoche, duc d'Abrantès, 1771-1813 (Box 114, Folder 2029)
    - Juvénal des Ursins, Jean, 1388-1473 (Box 114, Folder 2030)
    - Oversize
      - Ja - Jz general, 5 (Box 115 (Oversize), Folder 2031-2035)
      - Jackson - Jeannin, 11 (Box 116 (Oversize), Folder 2036-2046)
      - Jefferson - Juvénal, 21 (Box 117 (Oversize), Folder 2047-2067)
  - K
    - Ka - Kz general, 9 (Box 118, Folder 2068-2076)
    - Kant, Immanuel, 1724-1804 (Box 119, Folder 2077)
    - Kapodistrias, Iōannēs Antōniou, 1776-1831 (Box 119, Folder 2078)
    - Kaunitz-Rietberg, Wenzel Anton, Fürst, 1711-1794 (Box 119, Folder 2079)
    - Kean, Charles John, 1811?-1868 (Box 119, Folder 2080)
    - Kean, Edmund, 1787-1833 (Box 119, Folder 2081)
    - Keats, John, 1795-1821 (Box 119, Folder 2082)
    - Kelly
    - Kemble, Charles, 1775-1854 (Box 119, Folder 2083)
    - Kemble, Fanny, 1809-1893 (Box 119, Folder 2084)
    - Kemble, John Philip, 1757-1823 (Box 119, Folder 2085)
    - Kennett, White, 1660-1728 (Box 119, Folder 2086)
    - Kenton (Box 119, Folder 2087)
    - Khevenhüller (Box 119, Folder 2088)
    - Killigrew, Anne, 1660-1685 (Box 119, Folder 2089)
    - King, Rufus (all) (Box 119, Folder 2090)
    - Kingsley, Elbridge
    - Kléber, Jean-Baptiste, 1753-1800 (Box 119, Folder 2091)
    - Kleist (Box 119, Folder 2092)
    - Klopstock, Friedrich Gottlieb, 1724-1803 (Box 119, Folder 2093)
    - Knowlton, Thomas, 1740-1776
    - Knox, Henry, 1750-1806 (Box 119, Folder 2094)
    - Knox, John, ca. 1514-1572 (Box 119, Folder 2095)
    - Königsmarck (Box 119, Folder 2096)
    - Körner, Theodor, 1791-1813 (Box 119, Folder 2097)
    - Kollock, Henry (Box 119, Folder 2098)
    - Konstantin (Box 119, Folder 2099)
    - Kościuszko, Tadeusz, 1746-1817 (Box 119, Folder 2100)
    - Kotzebue, August von, 1761-1819 (Box 119, Folder 2101)
    - Kray von Krajova, Paul, Freiherr, 1735-1804 (Box 119, Folder 2102)
    - Kutuzov, Mikhail Illarionovich, svetleĭshiĭ kni︠a︡zʹ Smolenskiĭ, 1745-1813 (Box 119, Folder 2103)
    - Oversize
      - Ka - Kz general, 4 (Box 120 (Oversize), Folder 2104-2107)
      - Kant - Kray, 20 (Box 121 (Oversize), Folder 2108-2127)
  - L
    - La - Let general, 12 (Box 122, Folder 2128-2139)